<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Frequently Asked Questions :: Lumina Desktop Environment</title>
    <link>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/faq/index.html</link>
    <description>How is it different from other desktop environments? Originally designed to work best with TrueOS® and Project Trident®, but specifically works very well for the BSD community at large. Lumina® can also be easily ported to any OS, including Linux distros). Does not require any of the commonly used desktop implementation frameworks (DBUS, policykit, consolekit, systemd, HALD, etc..). Does not come bundled with any “end-user” applications (web browsers, email clients, multimedia software, office suites, etc..). The only utilities that Lumina brings to the table by default are the ones written specifically for the project and are generally for background/utilitarian functionality (the largest utility is the file manager). Simple text-based configuration file for setting system-wide defaults for new users. This allows distributors of the desktop to easily pre-set the system defaults/interface so it just works for the end user. Plugin-based interface design. This allows the user to make the desktop as light/heavy as desired (within reason) simply by choosing which plugins to have running on their desktop/panels. Designed to function as a general-purpose system interface – easily pre-configured to run on any type/size of device or screen. See the features page for additional details. What operating systems is it available for? Lumina is highly portable and should work on any Unix-like operating system, with a single OS-compatibility class for porters to check/update as necessary. It has already been ported to all the various BSD operating systems, as well as many of the Linux distributions.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2012-2021 : Ken Moore &amp; (c) 2021-2024 : JT Pennington</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://lumina-desktop.github.io/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
  </channel>
</rss>