<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ken Moore &amp; JT Pennington News</title>
    <link>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content from Ken Moore &amp; JT Pennington</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2012-2021 : Ken Moore &amp; (c) 2021-2022 : JT Pennington</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      
    <item>
      <title>Help requested for three big items for Lumina</title>
      <link>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2022-02-08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2022-02-08/</guid>
      <description>In this post I mentioned some of the major work that is on the road map for Lumina, and I&amp;rsquo;ve finally made the time to expand on this a little more.
In this post I&amp;rsquo;m going to cover three of the big ticket items I need help with.
However before I get into that, a few points worth mentioning. C++/Qt experience is a definite requirement. It&amp;rsquo;s not that I have anything against Python or Go, but Lumina is written with C++/Qt, so that&amp;rsquo;s what you&amp;rsquo;ll need to know.</description>
    </item>
      
    
      
    <item>
      <title>Lumina 1.6.2 released.</title>
      <link>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-12-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-12-25/</guid>
      <description>Another update to Lumina is out The next update to the Lumina Desktop is out!
Lumina Desktop v1.6.2
Updates in this release:
  Lumina-checkpass has been disabled. I mistakingly enabled this in the 1.6.1 release. After speaking with Ken about this, he reminded me that this is a part of the yet unifinished Unified Desktop. As such it is not needed with the current releases and has been disabled from being built by default.</description>
    </item>
      
    
      
    <item>
      <title>Lumina 1.6.1 released.</title>
      <link>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-10-05/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-10-05/</guid>
      <description>Yes the project is still alive. And in fact there&amp;rsquo;s been a release!
Lumina Desktop v1.6.1
It&amp;rsquo;s only been 611 days&amp;hellip; that&amp;rsquo;s not too long right?
Anyway onto the point, yes the project is still alive and there&amp;rsquo;s been some updates. This release encompases two main things.
First is a collection of minor fixes that have gone into master since 1.6.0 came out, along with some translation updates. This includes two small additional binaries for use by the desktop.</description>
    </item>
      
    
      
    <item>
      <title>Study the past if you would define the future.</title>
      <link>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-07-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-07-01/</guid>
      <description>History &amp;ldquo;Study the past if you would define the future.&amp;rdquo; ~Confucius
Before we discuss the Lumina Desktop today, lets first go back and discuss the past. The Lumina Desktop was started in 2012 by Ken Moore. He started working on it in his free time. He wanted to design a small lightweight desktop for PC-BSD that didn&amp;rsquo;t come with the challenge of dealing with Linux-isms. However instead of designing a desktop that had BSD-isms, he decided to design the desktop to be as OS agnostic as possible with as few dependecies as possible.</description>
    </item>
      
    
      
    <item>
      <title>Maintainership Change</title>
      <link>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-06-23/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lumina-desktop.github.io/post/2021-06-23/</guid>
      <description>After more than 7 years of work, I have decided that it is time to let others take over the development of the Lumina Desktop project going forward. It has been an incredible task which has pushed me into areas of development that I had never previously considered. However, with work and life changes, my time for developing new functionality for Lumina has become nearly non-existent, particularly for the Qt5 -&amp;gt; Qt6 change that will be coming within the next year or so.</description>
    </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
